

ABOUT ME

A multi-skilled and experienced Software Developer with an extensive track record of developing and maintaining high-quality software solutions. Possesses 8+ years of experience working in large and small organizations across a range of industrial sectors, including Education, Real Estate, Consulting and IT. Additionally has 5+ years of extensive experience developing websites, web applications and software.

LINKS

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/paul-osuigwe-loopcodes-82767a232

Twitter:

https://mobile.twitter.com/POsuigwe

GitHub:

https://github.com/Loopcodes

PROJECTS

Check out some of my projects @ https://loopcodes.netlify.app/

PAUL OSUIGWE {Loopcodes} Software Developer (FRONT-END)

8 Peace Estate Lekki, Lagos, 105102, Nigeria.



+234 807 491 6871



osuigwepaul.o@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

AUTARKY REAL ESTATE MANAGERS

Victoria Island, Lagos Dec 2021 – Present

Website developer

- Responsible for building, writing high-end reusable code and maintaining the agency's website
- Also in charge of all technical decisions and activities in the organization.

SHEILD & BUCKLER(S&B) DRYCLEANERS

Lekki, Lagos Jul 2020 – Dec 2021

Senior/Website developer

- I was entrusted with overseeing the progress of the development team and was also designated to handle all technical aspects of the organization.
- I also worked on the user-interface of the website, helping bring life to the organizations online image.
- Organized and oversaw a meeting with Sterling bank plc which helped seal a contract deal between both parties.

JUST CLEAN IT (JCI) DRYCLEANERS

Ajah, Lagos Jan 2020 – Jun 2021

Lead front-end developer

- I led a team of frontend developers to create a user-friendly website.
- As lead front-end developer, I was also charged with managing the site.

SIMPLYGOLDA INTERNATIONAL STORES

Lekki, Lagos Feb 2019 – Dec 2020

▶ Website developer/ Social media manager

- I built and managed the organization's website.
- With the knowledge I have about social media, I handled the company's social media accounts.
 Updating it from time to time based on the information given.

RAPID ACADEMY INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL

Lekki, Lagos Jan 2015 – Sep 2018

Computer teacher (Vacation job)

- Taught students to understand the basic concepts of computer science.
- Organized a science fair to help the students develop their various scientific skills.

REFERENCES

BARR. GOLDA OGUNO (CEO) Simplygolda international stores & Rapid academy international T: +234 802 222 8557

MRS. STELLA OTONO (CEO) **S&B** Cleaners Limited T: +234 803 310 3090

BARR. CHINYERE OBASI (CEO) **Covenant Solicitors & Associates T:** +234 803 564 9662

MR. GAVENTA OTONO Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) **T:** +234 809 853 1150

MR. UCHE AMAH Tenoil Energy T: +234 909 128 0055

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF NIGERIA, NSUKKA (UNN)

Enugu, Nigeria 2017 - 2021

Mathematics

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science and

ST. JAMES CATHEDRAL High school diploma **COLLEGE**

Ibadan, Nigeria 2011 - 2017

BEACON HOUSE SCHOOL

Lagos, Nigeria 2009 - 2011

LAURA STEPHENS SCHOOL

Lagos, Nigeria 2007 - 2009

OUR LADY OF MOUNT CARMEL NUR & PRY SCHOOL

Lagos, Nigeria 2005 - 2007

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML CSS, BOOTSTRAP, SASS

JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT **ANGULAR**

FIREBASE, JSON **GIT, GITHUB**

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

COMMUNICATION **I FADERSHIP**

TEAMWORK ADAPTABILITY

PROBLEM SOLVING RESEARCH

INTERNSHIP

XERDE LIMITED

Yaba, Nigeria Nov 2019 - Jan 2020

Junior front-end developer

- Worked with a team of highly experienced and amazing people to build a software application (Tudo) that helps people achieve their financial
- Learnt and understood the basics of Html, Css and Javascript.

HOBBIES













Reading

Travelling

Basketball

Music

Researching